bodog818.com 2014-03-06

# Privacy Policy | Bodog

  1. At Bodog, we believe in protecting the personal information provided by our account holders in the strictest manner. This is a legal document that sets out how Bodog handles the data which we collect to identify you. You should read this in conjunction with the Terms & Conditions, of which this Privacy Policy forms a part.
  2. Bodog endeavours to protect all your personal information and this data will not be sold or passed on to a third party.
  3. By registering your account with Bodog you acknowledge that you fully understand and accept the terms of use detailed in this policy when visiting our websites.
  4. The team at Bodog disapproves of SPAM and will never send you unsolicited emails. There may be some emails sent on a periodic basis to keep you updated and informed of any new Bodog products and services. These emails genuinely help you make the most of the website and let you know when there are new, fun and interesting promotions to take part in.
  5. Bodog uses small files known as “cookies” to enhance the account holder’s experience. To facilitate the optimal use of the Bodog Site, we may use a temporary “session” cookie. These cookies disappear when the member's browser session ends.
  6. Most internet browsers are automatically set up to accept cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse a cookie or ask your browser to show you where a cookie has been set up. Certain services are only activated by the presence of a cookie and if you choose to refuse cookies, particular features of this website may not be available to you.
  7. We also use cookies to compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use Bodog and to help us improve the structure of our website (we cannot identify you personally in this way).
  8. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide general site and non-personal statistical information about visits to pages on our sites. Bodog uses this type of information to help it improve the services to its members.
  9. We may share data supplied by you (or collected about you) with affiliate companies in the corporate group of which Bodog forms a part, but only for the purposes described in this policy.
  10. If all of the assets which Bodog uses to operate its business (or substantially all of them) are acquired by a third party, we may transfer personal data we then hold to that party so that the acquirer can continue to provide the same service.
  11. We have security measures in place to protect our customer database and access to this database is restricted internally. However, it remains each account holder’s responsibility to protect against unauthorised access, to ensure no-one else uses your Bodog login, to log off or exit from Bodog when not using the Site and to keep your password secret.
  12. Bodog reserves the right to communicate an account holder’s personal information to external parties when required to conform to legal requirements with which we are obliged by law to comply or when such information are required to complete and validate your transactions with our selected third party payment processors or financial institutions employed by Bodog.
  13. We will retain your personal data only as long as is necessary as per the requirements set forth in our Gaming License.
  14. If Bodog contains links to other sites, it is intended for informational purposes only. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those websites.
  15. Bodog reserve the right to change any information in this Privacy Policy at it sole discretion. Any changes to this document will be binding and effective immediately.
  16. This privacy policy was last updated on May 1st 2009.
